[
    {"question": "翼" , "answer": "wings", "sound":"tsubasa"},
    {"question": "朝", "answer": "morning", "sound":"asa"},
    {"question": "男", "answer": "man", "sound":"otoko"},
    {"question": "女", "answer": "woman", "sound":"onna"},
    {"question": "子", "answer": "child", "sound":"ko"},
    {"question": "獅子", "answer": "lion", "sound":"shishi"},
    {"question": "黒", "answer": "black", "sound":"kuro"},
    {"question": "紫", "answer": "purple", "sound":"murasaki"},
    {"question": "灰", "answer": "grey", "sound":"hai"},
    {"question": "車", "answer": "car", "sound":"kuruma"},
    {"question": "月曜日", "answer": "monday", "sound":"getsuyobi"},
    {"question": "火曜日", "answer": "tuesday", "sound":"kayobi"},
    {"question": "水曜日", "answer": "wednesday", "sound":"suiyobi"},
    {"question": "木曜日", "answer": "thursday", "sound":"mokuyobi"},
    {"question": "為", "answer": "purpose", "sound":"tame"},
    {"question": "金曜日", "answer": "friday", "sound":"kinyobi"},
    {"question": "土曜日", "answer": "saturday", "sound":"doyobi"},
    {"question": "日曜日", "answer": "sunday", "sound":"nichiyobi"},
    {"question": "財布", "answer": "wallet", "sound":"saifu"},
    {"question": "姉", "answer": "older sister", "sound":"ane"},
    {"question": "目", "answer": "eye", "sound":"me"},
    {"question": "火", "answer": "fire", "sound":"hi"},
    {"question": "水", "answer": "water", "sound":"mizu"},
    {"question": "古い", "answer": "old", "sound":"furuyi"},
    {"question": "若い", "answer": "young", "sound":"wakai"},
    {"question": "庭", "answer": "garden", "sound":"niwa"},
    {"question": "鳥", "answer": "bird", "sound":"tori"},
    {"question": "誰", "answer": "who", "sound":"dare"},
    {"question": "名前", "answer": "name", "sound":"namae"},
    {"question": "馬", "answer": "horse", "sound":"uma"},
    {"question": "鹿", "answer": "deer", "sound":"shika"},
    {"question": "傘", "answer": "umbrella", "sound":"kasa"},
    {"question": "火山", "answer": "volcano", "sound":"kazan"},
    {"question": "火山灰", "answer": "volcanic ash", "sound":"kazanbai"},
    {"question": "茶色", "answer": "brown", "sound":"chai iro"},
    {"question": "茶", "answer": "tea", "sound":"cha"},
    {"question": "赤ちゃん", "answer": "baby", "sound":"aka chan"},
    {"question": "赤い", "answer": "red", "sound":"akai"},
    {"question": "卵", "answer": "egg", "sound":"tamago"},
    {"question": "駅", "answer": "station", "sound":"eki"},
    {"question": "人間", "answer": "human", "sound":"ningen"},
    {"question": "犬", "answer": "dog", "sound":"inu"},
    {"question": "田中", "answer": "tanaka", "sound":"tanaka"},
    {"question": "猫", "answer": "cat", "sound":"neko"},
    {"question": "歌って", "answer": "sang", "sound":"uta te"},
    {"question": "方", "answer": "person", "sound":"kata"},
    {"question": "緑色", "answer": "green", "sound":"midori iro"},
    {"question": "体", "answer": "body", "sound":"karada"},
    {"question": "安い", "answer": "cheap", "sound":"yasui"},
    {"question": "休み", "answer": "to rest", "sound":"yasu mi"},
    {"question": "家", "answer": "house", "sound":"iie"},
    {"question": "待ちます", "answer": "to wait", "sound":"machi masu"},
    {"question": "椅子", "answer": "chair", "sound":"isu"},
    {"question": "声", "answer": "voice", "sound":"koe"},
    {"question": "会社", "answer": "company", "sound":"kaisha"},
    {"question": "肉", "answer": "meat", "sound":"nikku"},
    {"question": "植物", "answer": "plant", "sound":"shokubutsu"},
    {"question": "笑", "answer": "laugh", "sound":"wara"},
    {"question": "携帯", "answer": "phone", "sound":"denwa"},
    {"question": "消しゴム", "answer": "eraser", "sound":"keshigomu"},
    {"question": "開けて", "answer": "to open", "sound":"akete"},
    {"question": "閉めて", "answer": "to close", "sound":"shimete"},
    {"question": "質感", "answer": "texture", "sound":"shitsukan"},
    {"question": "次", "answer": "next", "sound":"tsugi"},
    {"question": "大学", "answer": "university", "sound":"daigaku"},
    {"question": "牛肉", "answer": "beef", "sound":"gyudon"},
    {"question": "秋", "answer": "autumn", "sound":"aki"},
    {"question": "夏", "answer": "summer", "sound":"natsu"},
    {"question": "冬", "answer": "winter", "sound":"fuyu"},   
    {"question": "春", "answer": "spring", "sound":"haru"},   
    {"question": "北", "answer": "north", "sound":"hoku"},
    {"question": "南", "answer": "south", "sound":"minami"},
    {"question": "西", "answer": "west", "sound":"nishi"},
    {"question": "東", "answer": "east", "sound":"higashi"},
    {"question": "化石", "answer": "fossil", "sound":"kaseki"},
    {"question": "死", "answer": "death", "sound":"shi"},
    {"question": "崩れる", "answer": "to crumble", "sound":"kuzureru"},
    {"question": "階", "answer": "floor (level)", "sound":"kai"},
    {"question": "泣いて", "answer": "cry", "sound":"naite"}, 
    {"question": "屋", "answer": "roof", "sound":"yane"}, 
    {"question": "床", "answer": "floor", "sound":"yuka"}, 
    {"question": "島", "answer": "island", "sound":"shima"}, 
    {"question": "本棚", "answer": "bookshelf", "sound":"hondana"}, 
    {"question": "思う", "answer": "to feel (think)", "sound":"omou"}, 
    {"question": "考えて", "answer": "to think", "sound":"kangaete"}, 
    {"question": "骸骨", "answer": "skeleton", "sound":"gaekotsu"}, 
    {"question": "骨", "answer": "bone", "sound":"hone"}, 
    {"question": "油", "answer": "oil", "sound":"abura"}, 
    {"question": "地元", "answer": "local", "sound":"jimoto"}, 
    {"question": "新聞", "answer": "newspaper", "sound":"shinbun"}, 
    {"question": "自転車", "answer": "bicycle", "sound":"jitensha"}, 
    {"question": "電車", "answer": "train", "sound":"densha"}, 
    {"question": "売って", "answer": "sold", "sound":"utte"}, 
    {"question": "買う", "answer": "buy", "sound":"kau"}, 
    {"question": "川", "answer": "river", "sound":"kawa"}, 
    {"question": "地面", "answer": "ground", "sound":"jimen"}, 
    {"question": "週末", "answer": "weekend", "sound":"shuumatsu"}, 
    {"question": "夜", "answer": "night", "sound":"yoru"}, 
    {"question": "微笑む", "answer": "smile", "sound":"hohoemu"}, 
    {"question": "行く", "answer": "to go (somewhere)", "sound":"iku"}, 
    {"question": "来る", "answer": "to come ", "sound":"kuru"}, 
    {"question": "別", "answer": "different", "sound":"betsu"}, 
    {"question": "別々", "answer": "separately", "sound":"betsubetsu"}, 
    {"question": "腕", "answer": "arm", "sound":"ude"}, 
    {"question": "腕前", "answer": "skill", "sound":"udemae"}, 
    {"question": "残業", "answer": "overtime", "sound":"zangyou"}, 
    {"question": "大人", "answer": "adult", "sound":"otona"}, 
    {"question": "充電器", "answer": "charger", "sound":"jyudenki"}, 
    {"question": "武器", "answer": "weapon", "sound":"bukki"}, 
    {"question": "自分", "answer": "oneself", "sound":"jibun"}, 
    {"question": "足", "answer": "legs", "sound":"ashi"}, 
    {"question": "足元", "answer": "foot", "sound":"ashimoto"}, 
    {"question": "コンセント", "answer": "electrical outlet", "sound":"consento"}, 
    {"question": "秒", "answer": "second (counter for seconds)", "sound":"byou"}, 
    {"question": "その他", "answer": "other", "sound":"sonohoka"}, 
    {"question": "長い", "answer": "long", "sound":"nagai"}, 
    {"question": "短い", "answer": "short", "sound":"mijikai"}, 
    {"question": "豆", "answer": "bean", "sound":"mame"}, 
    {"question": "深さ", "answer": "depth", "sound":"fukasa"}, 
    {"question": "ちらみせ", "answer": "glimpse", "sound":"chiramise"}, 
    {"question": "災害", "answer": "disaster", "sound":"saigai"}, 
    {"question": "窓", "answer": "window", "sound":"mado"}, 
    {"question": "社会", "answer": "society", "sound":"shakai"}, 
    {"question": "社長", "answer": "ceo", "sound":"shachou"}, 
    {"question": "妹", "answer": "little sister", "sound":"imouto"}, 
    {"question": "信号", "answer": "signal", "sound":"shingou"}, 
    {"question": "落ちた", "answer": "fell", "sound":"ochita"}, 
    {"question": "弱い", "answer": "weak", "sound":"yowai"}, 
    {"question": "大丈夫", "answer": "ok", "sound":"daijyoubou"}, 
    {"question": "モビルバッテリー", "answer": "power bank", "sound":"mobiru battery"}, 
    {"question": "お知らせ", "answer": "notice", "sound":"oshirase"}, 
    {"question": "早い", "answer": "fast (speed)", "sound":"hayai"}, 
    {"question": "会見", "answer": "press conference", "sound":"kaiken"}, 
    {"question": "お風呂", "answer": "bath", "sound":"ofurou"}, 
    {"question": "台所", "answer": "kitchen", "sound":"daidokorou"}, 
    {"question": "廊下", "answer": "passage", "sound":"rouka"}, 
    {"question": "点", "answer": "point", "sound":"ten"}, 
    {"question": "虫", "answer": "insect", "sound":"mushi"}, 
    {"question": "独立", "answer": "independence", "sound":"dokuritsu"}, 
    {"question": "終る", "answer": "end", "sound":"owaru"}, 
    {"question": "残る", "answer": "remain", "sound":"nokoru"}, 
    {"question": "請求書", "answer": "bill", "sound":"seikyuushou"}, 
    {"question": "ラジオ", "answer": "radio", "sound":"rajio"}, 
    {"question": "たんす", "answer": "chest of drawers", "sound":"tansu"}
]